Oyekola Oyedele

Email: kolaoyedele@icloud.com

Phone: (423) 353-7123 Location: Knoxville, TN 37932

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/kola-oyedele-86854910

GitHub: https://github.com/kolinzo1

SUMMARY

Shrewd and pragmatic data analyst, with more than 3-years' experience in data ETL, well educated in information technology, engineering, project management, and data analytics. Certified Salesforce Administrator. Well versed in programming, R, Python, VBA, HTML, SQL, JavaScript, Git, and APEX. Able to work independently in an ever-changing environment; Innovative; and Collaborative.

SKILLS

Data Analytics | Data Visualization | Machine Learning | Critical Analysis | Problem Solving | Programming | Database Querying | Quantitative Modeling | Statistical Analysis | Critical Thinking | Collaboration | Troubleshooting | Research and Development | Implementation | Leadership | Strategic Thinking | Business Analysis | Teamwork | Organization.

PROJECTS

- 1. Medical Deserts Determination and Impact in the US
- 2. Mapping Earthquakes
- 3. World Weather Analysis

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

R | Python | Pandas | Matplotlib | Machine Learning | SQL | PostgreSQL | ETL | VBA | HTML | JavaScript | APEX | Microsoft Office | MS Word | MS Excel | MS Outlook | MS PowerPoint | MS Access | MS SharePoint | Salesforce | Oracle | Tableau | social media | LinkedIn | OneDrive | WeTransfer | Google Docs | Google Sheets

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Vanderbilt University | Nashville, TN BootCamp - Data Analytics

Dec. 2020 – June 2021

Certificate

• Relevant Classes: Excel, VBA, Python, Pandas, Matplotlib, Python APIs, Machine Learning, SQL, ETL, MongoDB, JavaScript. Big Data

Walters State Community College | Morristown, TN

A.A.S., Health Information Management

Aug. 2018 - Present

Relevant Experience: Practice Management Software, EPIC, EHR Management Systems, 3M Encoder

Obafemi Awolowo University | Nigeria

B.S., Chemical Engineering

Certification: Salesforce Administration

EXPERIENCE

Cherokee Health Systems | Knoxville, TN

Research Data Analyst

Mar. 2020 - Present

- Designed a report template for weekly MCM reporting.
- Maintained REDCap database to ensure data quality and consistency.
- Designed and maintained a tracking system for the Operation Vaccination program.

- Collaborate with external agencies on a day-to-day basis regarding reporting and data analysis.
- Built analysis and reporting for COVID Counseling Program.

Express Employment Professionals Production Team Member

June 2017 - Oct. 2018

Two K. Netlink, Ltd. | Nigeria Project Coordinator

Jan. 2003 - Oct. 2014

• Responsible for the successful execution of a running service contract for the installation of Base Transmission Stations and associated services for major telecoms network with over 450 cell site installations.